<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Megan Whiting</title>
    <link>https://megan.ieuanjenkins.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Megan Whiting</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 13:20:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://megan.ieuanjenkins.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s Talk Wedding Poetry!</title>
      <link>https://megan.ieuanjenkins.com/2019/05/lets-talk-wedding-poetry/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 13:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://megan.ieuanjenkins.com/2019/05/lets-talk-wedding-poetry/</guid>
      <description>With wedding season fast approaching, I thought it might be helpful to talk about my personalised poetry in a little more detail.
More often than not, I’m contacted by brides looking for a bespoke poem to take the place of a reading at their wedding ceremony, but I’ve also written poems for key members of the wedding party to give the newlyweds as a unique gift! Printed on parchment-style paper, the poems look lovely when framed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Tips for the Self-Employed</title>
      <link>https://megan.ieuanjenkins.com/2019/03/30-tips-for-the-self-employed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 11:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://megan.ieuanjenkins.com/2019/03/30-tips-for-the-self-employed/</guid>
      <description>It’s safe to say that self-employment and working from home can be challenging at times…!
Below are 30 tips I’ve pulled together for the benefit of fellow self-employed folk; especially those who are new to this lifestyle.
So, without further ado…
Tip 1 Try to get up at a similar (and sensible!) time each morning. When your workspace is a mere few metres away, it can be tempting to stay in bed a little longer, but it’s important to establish a routine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Love with Books</title>
      <link>https://megan.ieuanjenkins.com/2019/02/in-love-with-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 08:33:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://megan.ieuanjenkins.com/2019/02/in-love-with-books/</guid>
      <description>Book Benefits I’ve found comfort and enjoyment in books for as long as I can remember, and, fortunately for me, as a writer, proofreader and editor, I get to read on a daily basis! Luckily, reading as part of my job hasn’t quelled my appetite for books and I still read an awful lot; for pleasure, escapism and as a way of de-stressing!
Even now, I come across words I feel compelled to look up; either because they’re unfamiliar, or I’m not sure how to pronounce them, as I’ve only ever seen them written down&amp;hellip; !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proofreading and Editing</title>
      <link>https://megan.ieuanjenkins.com/proofreading-and-editing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 17:10:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://megan.ieuanjenkins.com/proofreading-and-editing/</guid>
      <description>Whether you are a self-publishing author seeking an editor for your manuscript or a student looking for a proofreader for a CV, thesis or dissertation, I can provide you with a professional service at an affordable cost.
Before work begins, I offer a free sample proofread or edit, followed by a fixed quote, so that my clients know exactly what to budget for. All quotes include a final read-through of the document once suggestions have been reviewed by the client, leaving no stone unturned!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wedding Poetry</title>
      <link>https://megan.ieuanjenkins.com/wedding-poetry/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 17:10:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://megan.ieuanjenkins.com/wedding-poetry/</guid>
      <description>Let me make your wedding day even more special with a bespoke poem personalised to yourself and your partner.
Once I&amp;rsquo;ve asked you a few questions relating to the style and content of the poem you&amp;rsquo;ve been imagining (for example, a romantic, rhyming poem with 4 verses or a light-hearted, non-rhyming piece) I can create something which fully reflects your sentiments and will only ever be heard at your wedding!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Copywriting</title>
      <link>https://megan.ieuanjenkins.com/copywriting/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jan 2019 17:08:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://megan.ieuanjenkins.com/copywriting/</guid>
      <description>I can help you attract customers to your business and keep them coming back with vibrant copy tailored to the needs of your readership; either through creating new content, or refreshing yours.
With my background in creative writing, I can really spice up your web content and help you sell your product or service! My friendly, informal blog posts will add a sense of personality to your website, whilst offering advice to the reader.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Author&#39;s Guide to Proofreading and Editing</title>
      <link>https://megan.ieuanjenkins.com/2019/01/the-authors-guide-to-proofreading-and-editing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://megan.ieuanjenkins.com/2019/01/the-authors-guide-to-proofreading-and-editing/</guid>
      <description>It’s the start of a new year! Have you made any resolutions?
Perhaps you’re planning to self-publish the book you spent most of 2018 writing, but know that it needs a little fine-tuning, in the form of a proofread or edit?
It’s important to understand that although proofreading and editing have their similarities, there are key differences between the two.
I provide both services, but you may come across professionals specialising in either proofreading or editing, so it is a good idea to familiarise yourself with the terms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://megan.ieuanjenkins.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://megan.ieuanjenkins.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>For an informal discussion about your project or to view my portfolio, please get in touch via the contact form.
Alternatively, you can reach me through Facebook, Twitter or email (see links above) or just give me a call!
Whether you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a commercial writer to provide you with engaging web content or blog posts, a creative writer to craft you a personalised, bespoke wedding poem, or a reliable proofreader or editor, I can provide you with a professional service to suit your budget.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Background</title>
      <link>https://megan.ieuanjenkins.com/my-background/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://megan.ieuanjenkins.com/my-background/</guid>
      <description>I have loved reading and writing for as long as I can remember, so was delighted to achieve a degree in English Literature and Creative Writing with the Open University in 2015!
I later developed an interest in proofreading/editing and joined the Society for Editors and Proofreaders. To date, I have worked on a range of manuscripts, including fantasy novels, self-development books, memoirs, young adult fiction, animated film scripts; even a political parody!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>