<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Articles on Megan Whiting</title>
    <link>https://megan.ieuanjenkins.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Articles on Megan Whiting</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 10:58:08 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://megan.ieuanjenkins.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Tips for the Self-Employed</title>
      <link>https://megan.ieuanjenkins.com/2019/03/30-tips-for-the-self-employed/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2019 11:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://megan.ieuanjenkins.com/2019/03/30-tips-for-the-self-employed/</guid>
      <description>It’s safe to say that self-employment and working from home can be challenging at times…!
Below are 30 tips I’ve pulled together for the benefit of fellow self-employed folk; especially those who are new to this lifestyle.
So, without further ado…
Tip 1 Try to get up at a similar (and sensible!) time each morning. When your workspace is a mere few metres away, it can be tempting to stay in bed a little longer, but it’s important to establish a routine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Love with Books</title>
      <link>https://megan.ieuanjenkins.com/2019/02/in-love-with-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 08:33:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://megan.ieuanjenkins.com/2019/02/in-love-with-books/</guid>
      <description>Book Benefits I’ve found comfort and enjoyment in books for as long as I can remember, and, fortunately for me, as a writer, proofreader and editor, I get to read on a daily basis! Luckily, reading as part of my job hasn’t quelled my appetite for books and I still read an awful lot; for pleasure, escapism and as a way of de-stressing!
Even now, I come across words I feel compelled to look up; either because they’re unfamiliar, or I’m not sure how to pronounce them, as I’ve only ever seen them written down&amp;hellip; !</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Author&#39;s Guide to Proofreading and Editing</title>
      <link>https://megan.ieuanjenkins.com/2019/01/the-authors-guide-to-proofreading-and-editing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://megan.ieuanjenkins.com/2019/01/the-authors-guide-to-proofreading-and-editing/</guid>
      <description>It’s the start of a new year! Have you made any resolutions?
Perhaps you’re planning to self-publish the book you spent most of 2018 writing, but know that it needs a little fine-tuning, in the form of a proofread or edit?
It’s important to understand that although proofreading and editing have their similarities, there are key differences between the two.
I provide both services, but you may come across professionals specialising in either proofreading or editing, so it is a good idea to familiarise yourself with the terms.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>